（圭一(けいいち)）んっ もう朝か
It's already morning?
Morning...
朝… んっ？
Wait, it's already this late?!
って もうこんな時間かよ！
ま… まずい！
Crap!!
We were supposed to meet at the pool, weren't we?
た… 確か
プールに直接集合だったよな
アハハッ これなら余裕で楽勝だぜ
Now that I've made it this far,
getting there on time will be a piece of cake...
アハハッ あっ
（ブレーキ音）
うわあ！ 海パン忘れた！
I forgot my swim trunks!!
You could always swim buck naked.
（魅音(みおん)）すっぽんぽんで泳げば？
Keiichi-kun's fur seal is so cute... I wanna take it home!
圭一君のオットセイ かぁいいよお
お持ち帰り～
That'd be terrifying...  Absolutely terrifying!
恐ろしい 恐ろしすぎる
どうすればいいんだ！
What should I do?!
（善朗(よしろう)）そうかい
（圭一）わっ
Is that so?
プールに行くのに
海パンを忘れたのかい
Going to the pool but forgot to bring your
swim trunks, did you?  That must be tough...
それは難儀だ
M-Mion's uncle?
み… 魅音のおじさん
そ… そうなんです
Yeah, I did...
どっかこの辺で
海パンが買える所って…
Do you happen to know any places
around here where I could buy a pair...?
前原(まえばら)君は実に運がいい フフフ…
Maebara-kun, today's your lucky day...
Tada!!
（善朗）
じゃーん！ どうだい？ 新品だよ
How do you like 'em?
They're brand new, you know!
よかったら
前原君にプレゼントしよう
If you want, I could give 'em to you as a present.
Oh man, swim trunks!
おお！ 海パンだあ！
柄が何だかヘンテコだが
この際どうでもいい
The design's a little weird, but at this point, who cares!
実は この海パン
ただの海パンじゃないんだ
Actually, these aren't just any old swim trunks! They're called
"ladies' man swim trunks" – they're magic, you see!
モテモテの海パンという
魔法の海パンでねえ
Ladies' man swim trunks...?
モテモテの海パン？
Well, you see...  If the wearer writes his name on these and then plays in the pool for three hours,
これにね 名前を書いて
３時間プールで遊べば―
はいてる人間に
モテモテの魔法がかかるんだ
he'll come under the effects of the ladies' man magic!
う… うさんくさいですね
That sounds pretty suspicious...
It does, doesn't it?  That's why I've been a
little worried about trying them on myself...
うさんくさいよねえ
だから自分で試すのは
ちょっと不安でね
So you wanna test it out by making me try 'em on?
んで 俺に はかせて試させようと？
Well, it's not like I'm forcing you to...
まあ 無理にとは言わないけどね
ああ 今朝ね 魅音ちゃんが来て―
Oh, by the way... This morning, Mion-chan came by to pick up a pair of swim trunks she ordered...
取り寄せた海パンを
受け取っていったんだよ
She did?  To pick up swim trunks?
魅音が海パン？
You should have seen 'em, with that swan throwing its head back in such a manly way...
あんな雄々しく反り返った
白鳥の海パンなんて―
よっぽどの罰ゲーム用なんだろうね
I'll bet they're for some crazy punishment game!
Swan swim trunks...  Ladies' man swim trunks...  It's either one or the other at this point, isn't it?
（善朗）
白鳥の海パンかモテモテの海パンか
もう どっちかしかないね
くっ くうう…
（善朗）んっ？
Alright.  I'll borrow those ladies' man swim trunks.
わ… 分かりました
そのモテモテ海パンを借ります
But of course you will!
うん だよねえ
Here you go!
（善朗）はい
This kinda makes it feel like I'm signing a contract with the devil...
な… なんか悪魔の契約書に
署名する気分だぜ
Mae...bara... Kei...ichi...
前… 原… 圭… 一っと
Oh yeah, during the three hours until the ladies' man magic sinks into your body...
ああ それとね―
君の体にモテモテの魔法が
宿るまでの３時間なんだけど―
どうやら試練もあるらしいんだ
（圭一）試練？
It seems you will have to overcome a series of trials.
Trials?
Well, you see...
なんでもね モテない男たちの
怨念も宿っているらしくてね
They say these swim trunks harbor the hateful grudge of all the men who were never able to become popular with the ladies...
（圭一）んっ！
（善朗）３時間の間に―
During those three hours, they'll come after you using every trick in the book to try and strip those trunks off of you!
何とか君の海パンを脱がそうと―
あの手この手で
襲いかかってくるらしいんだ！
Forget suspicious... These swim trunks
just sound freakin' dangerous now...
うさんくさいを通り越して―
めちゃくちゃヤバそうな
海パンなんすけど
Three hours!  If you can last that long in these swim trunks, the ladies' man magic will be yours.
（善朗）
３時間 海パンをはいたまま
無事に乗り越えられれば―
君の体にはモテモテの魔法が宿る
What do you think?  Sounds like a pretty intense game, doesn't it!
どうだい なかなか熱い勝負だろ？
Alright!  At any rate, I've got swim trunks!  Now I've got to dash over to the pool!
やったあ！
ともあれ海パン ゲーット！
あとはプールへダーッシュ！
Shall I let you in on a secret?
教えましょうか
Oshiemashou ka?
In return, promise me you won't tell anyone else
その代わり誰にも　言わない約束してね
Sono kawari dare ni mo iwanai yakusoku shite ne
Hold your little finger to mine and swear, lie and it's a thousand needles
指切りげんまん　嘘ついたら針千本
Yubikiri genman, uso tsuitara hari senbon
Take the convoluted story
折りたたまれたまま蠢いている物語を
Oritatamareta mama ugomeiteiru monogatari wo
spread it out and show it to me
広げて見せてよ
Hirogete misete yo
The past and the future are
過去も未来も
Kako mo mirai mo
a superscription of data
Super scription of data
Shame Exposing Chapter
Okinomiya
City Pool
ハハハハハッ
前原圭一 ただいま参上！
Maebara Keiichi has now arrived!
Keiichi!  We've been waiting for you!
（梨花(りか)）圭一 待ちましたのですよ
Well, I suppose you made it, barely.
（沙都子(さとこ)）
まあ ギリギリセーフという
ところですわね
残念 遅刻したら―
Too bad!  And we had a special punishment game ready, just in case you were late!
スペシャルな罰ゲームを
用意してたんだけどねえ
Heh!  As if I'd let you make me wear swim trunks with a swan on 'em!
（圭一）けっ 白鳥の海パンなんて
はかされてたまるかよ
さあ 混みだす前に
思いっきり遊び倒そうぜ！
All right, let's have fun before the crowds get here!
（魅音たち）おーう！
（圭一）ムフフフ～ たまら～ん
This is awesome! Rena's swimsuit is a daring bikini-type! She looks a little embarrassed, but that's the best part!
レナの水着は
ちょっぴり大胆なビキニタイプか
さすがに ちいっと
恥ずかしそうにしてるが―
それが またいい！
赤らめたレナの表情には
グッと来るものがあるぜ
I love how she blushes!
And Mion's swimsuit...
そして 魅音の水着は―
...is an unusual Chinese dress style swimsuit!
チャイナドレスみたいな
変わった水着だ
The way it lets you catch little glimpses of her inner thighs is a hundred times better than having them in full view!
チラチラと見える内ももが
露出しているより100倍 萌(も)える！
But more than anything, those huge
dangling melons take it over the top!
何よりも その たゆんたゆんする
巨大な２つのメロンは反則だあ！
And then we have Satoko!
さらに沙都子は―
It's hard to dismiss how, at such a young age, she already has lines that promise a voluptuous future!
この年で早くも豊満な未来を
予想させるラインは侮り難し
And despite that, the gap created by her
childish-looking swimsuit is just tremendous!
そのくせ幼さを感じさせる水着との
ギャップがすさまじい！
For those of a certain taste,
this combination is just plain dangerous!
その道の属性の連中なら
この組み合わせは極めて危険
And last but not least is... Rika-chan!
極めつけは 梨花ちゃんだあ
Her lines may be like that of an as-yet-unripe fruit,
まだまだ未熟な 青い果実を
思わせるラインなのに―
but her daring bikini style is something to be feared!
大胆なビキニスタイルとは
恐れ入るぜ
そして大事なのはヒモ！
And most importantly, the strings! What man wouldn't want to pull one of those strings just once?!
そのヒモを 男なら一度は
引っ張ってみたいと思う
Ahh... I want to pull them... want to pull them...
ああ 引っ張りたい
引っ張りたい
圭一が いやらしい想像を
しているのです
Keiichi, you're thinking something naughty!  I'll just
have to let you and your dirty thoughts go in first then!
そんな不潔な圭一には
先を譲るのですよ
ええいっ
（圭一）うわっ うああ！
Take that!
にいっ ふおっ ひっほっはっ
いい うおお ああ！
アッハハハハッ
（チャイム）
（魅音）よおしっ あたしも！
Alright!  My turn!
May I have your attention, please.
（アナウンス）
お客様のお呼び出しを申し上げます
園崎(そのざき)魅音様
お電話が入っております
We have received a phone call for Sonozaki Mion-san.  Would she please come to the main office?
中央事務室までお越しください
魅ぃちゃん 呼ばれてるよ
Mii-chan, they're calling your name.
Wonder what it is...  I'll be right back!
何だろ？ 行ってくるわ
Hello, this is Mion.
（魅音）はい 魅音ですけど
Oh, Uncle Yoshiro from the toy shop!  What's up?
ああ おもちゃ屋の善朗おじさん
どうしたの？
This is really bad, Mion-chan!  I made a huge mistake!
大変なんだ 魅音ちゃん
えらいことをしてしまった
What?!  Magic swim trunks?
はあ？ 魔法の海パン!?
That's right!
そうなんだ 海パンにね
名前を書くんだけど―
So you write a name on 'em, right?
その名前の人が
海パンをはいている人を―
But it turns out the person with that name will fall in love with the person wearing the swim trunks!
好きになっちゃうらしいんだよ
ああ なんてことだ
God, what've I done!
And I made Maebara-kun write his name on 'em, too!!
そこに前原君の名前を
書かせちゃったんだよ
So you're saying that Kei-chan will fall in love with Kei-chan?
つまり 圭ちゃんが圭ちゃんを
好きになっちゃうってこと？
It was written right here in the manual, but I completely missed it!
ちゃんと説明書に書いてあったのに
見落としてたんだよ
So this means...
ってことは…
He'll spend the rest of his life just staring at his face in a
mirror - a dangerous narcissist, off in his own little world!
（善朗）彼は 一生ひたすら鏡で
自分の顔を見て うっとり陶酔―
危ない魔空間大好き―
ナルシストさんに
なるってことなんだよ！
Hi~
ハ～イ
Isn't that the complete opposite of what it's supposed to do?!
それって
まったくの逆効果じゃないのさあ
That's why you gotta strip 'em off!  If he keeps 'em on for over three hours, it'll be too late!
だから脱がせるんだよ
３時間 はき続けたら
もう手遅れになる
Let's see... It's been almost an hour already...
（魅音）ええっと もうすぐ１時間
Then you only have two hours left!! Mion-chan, you've got to pull off those swim trunks!
（善朗）
じゃあ あと２時間しかない
魅音ちゃん
彼の海パンを脱がせてくれ！
Kei-chan, spending the rest of his life staring at a mirror, lost in his own image...
圭ちゃんが一生
鏡見て自分に うっとり？
女の子には見向きもしないなんて…
Not giving even the slightest attention to women...!
Oh yeah...
うっふ～ん
I can't let that happen!!
（魅音）そんなの まずいよお
Okay!  I'll think of something.
分かったよ 何とかするよ！
...and that's how it is.
（魅音）…という話なんだよ
（圭一）マ… マジかよ その話！
Are you serious?
These aren't "ladies' man" swim trunks at all!
何がモテモテの海パンだよ
But if I take these off, then I won't have any swim trunks...
だけど これ脱いだら
俺の海パンは…
はぅ～
まさか 魅ぃちゃん あれ？
Mii-chan, you don't think we could use that, do you?
You don't know how lucky you are, Kei-chan!  We've got a replacement pair of swim trunks ready for you!
なんて圭ちゃんは
ラッキーなんだろう
代わりの水着は用意してある
げげっ！ もしかして それって
白鳥の海パン？
Don't tell me they're those swan swim trunks... Are they?
Oh my!  How did you know?
あら なんで知ってますの？
そうか 分かったぞ
お前らのたくらみ
I get it.  I see what you guys are up to!
その恥ずかしい白鳥の海パンを
俺に はかせたくって―
You just thought up this little story because you want me to wear those embarrassing swan swim trunks, didn't you?
そんな作り話を考えやがったな
What??  I'm just telling you what my uncle told me...!
はあ？
私は おじさんの伝言を…
なるほど
Oh, is that so!
これが おもちゃ屋のおじさんの
言っていた―
I guess this is what the old man from the toy store meant when he was talking about the "trials"...
モテない男たちの怨念で
試練ってやつなんだな
I'd have to overcome because of the hateful grudge of all the men who were never popular with the ladies!
W-What're you talking about, Kei-chan?
な… 何言ってんだよ 圭ちゃん
へへーん
こいつを脱がしたいのか？
You wanna take these babies off? Are you afraid that all the girls in the world would be swooning over me?
俺が世界中のギャルに モテモテに
なっちまうのが怖いのか？
フフンッ
Kei-chan, you idiot!
圭ちゃんのバカ！
そのまま あと２時間
その海パンをはき続けたら―
If you keep wearing those for another two hours, you'll end up like one of those weirdos who only love themselves!
圭ちゃんは
自分だけが大好きな―
オッペケペー野郎に
なっちゃうんだよ
If you wanna take these babies off, you're gonna have to come and get 'em!  See ya!
こいつを脱がしたかったら
実力で来やがれってんだ
じゃあな ふっ！
Kei-chan!!
あっ 圭ちゃん！
I don't know about you, but I think it would be
interesting to see Keiichi go all ga-ga over himself!
ボク的には 自分に うっとり
ニタニタしてる圭一も―
面白いと思いますですよ にぱ～
ダ… ダメだよ
そんなの全然 健全じゃないよ！
No way!  That's so wrong!
In any case, the fact that he's
outright refusing to take them off...
とりあえず
絶対脱がないと言われますと―
無理にでも
脱がしてやりたくなるのが―
is enough to make me want to strip them off even if I didn't have to! That's the very spirit of our club, wouldn't you say?
部活魂でございますわねえ
みぃ プールの ど真ん中で―
We'll make a game out of showing off
Kei-chan's fur seal in the middle of the pool!
圭一のオットセイを
さらし者にしてやるのです
ああ 圭一君のためだもん
圭一君のためだもん
It's for his own good!  It's for his own good!  We have no choice!
これは しかたないことだもん
All right...  Since we have no choice...
よしっ しかたないね
I call together the club members!
ここに部活メンバーを招集！
圭ちゃんを呪われた
魔法の海パンから解放するため―
In order to free Kei-chan from the cursed magical swim trunks, we will commence an assault operation!
強襲作戦を開始する！
Understood, ma'am!
はっ 了解でございますわ
ンフフフフフ… 羽入(はにゅう)
あんたも手伝いなさい
Hanyuu.  You help out, too.
Wh-What?! Rika, that's going too far! It's downright dirty!
り… 梨花 それは鬼なのです
まさに外道なのですよお
If you help stop him from getting away, I'll let you taste cream puffs every day, plus I'll treat you to Angel Mort's Jumbo Platter.
逃げるのを阻止してくれたら
夏休みの間 毎日シュークリーム
さらにエンジェルモートの
特製ジャンボシュー
I'll definitely stop him! I'll teach Keiichi the foolishness of defying a god!
絶対阻止してみせるのです
神に逆らうことの愚かさを
圭一に思い知らせてあげるのですよ
ンフフフフ… 面白くなってきたわ
Now things are getting interesting...
Leave it to me!
任せるのです
プハッ ヘヘヘッ
What's wrong?  I'm right over here!
どうした？ 俺はこっちだぞ
んっ へへーん
Why do you have to be so fast!
んっ
なんてすばしっこいんだよ！
（圭一）ほらほら
どうした こっちだぞ
（沙都子）圭一さんの分際で
今日は絶好調でございますのね
For someone like Keiichi-san, he sure is doing well today.
へへーん
（沙都子）圭一さんの分際で
今日は絶好調でございますのね
ほらほら
どうした どうした
I'm gonna take home Keiichi-kun's fur seal!
（レナ）圭一君のオットセイ
お持ち帰り～
アハハハハハッ
こっちだぞ
早く捕まえて 圭一の海パンを
引きずり下ろすのです みぃ
We've got to hurry up and pull down Keiichi's swim trunks!
See you later, Youth Detective Squad!
さらばだ 少年探偵団諸君
タハハハハハ
He's not trying to leave the pool, is he?!
まさかプールを出ていく気!?
We won't let him.  Hanyuu!
させないわ 羽入！
Time, stop!
（羽入）時間よ 止まれ！
And now, I can take this opportunity to change Keiichi's direction...
で この間に圭一の向きを…
よいしょ よいしょっと
はい 解除 パンッ
And done!
ハハハッ ぬあっ くっ おっ
This is all for the Special Jumbo Platter. Please forgive me, Keiichi!
これも
特製ジャンボシューのためなのです
許すのです 圭一 にぱ～
プハッ な… なんで？
どうなってんだ？
What the...?  What's going on here?!
Hold it right there, Keiichi-san!
（沙都子）お待ちなさい 圭一さん
（圭一）んっ
げっ あ… あと２時間
逃げ切れば―
If I can make it just two more hours, I'll be blessed with magic that'll make me popular with all the girls in the world!
世界中のギャルに
モテモテになる魔法が授かるんだ
That's right! When I make it through these trials, I'll be the most popular man in the world!
そうだ この試練を見事乗り越えて
是が非でもモテモテになってやるぜ
Kei-chan!  Why don't you just grow up and let us catch you already?
圭ちゃん
おとなしく捕まってったら
本気の圭一君が相手じゃ
とても捕まえられないよ
When Keiichi-kun gets serious he's really hard to catch...
We need reinforcements!
もっと応援が必要ですわ
（魅音）応援か
Reinforcements, huh...
（鷹野(たかの)）ハア
It's Takano Miyo-san!
鷹野三四(みよ)さんだ
There's no mistaking that outrageous body.  It
should be against the law to have boobs that big!
あのけしからんボディーは
間違いない 巨乳禁止法違反
あっ あらあら
魅音ちゃんたちじゃない 奇遇ねえ
My! My! If it isn't Mion-chan and her little friends!  What a coincidence!
Actually, we have some information we think you'd be interested in hearing!
おーっほっほっほ
実は 鷹野さんに
耳寄りな情報がございますのよ
Oh, I wonder what it could be!
あら 何かしら？
（沙都子）こしょ こしょ
こしょ こしょ こしょ
はっ 何ですって!?
What did you say?!
前原君のはいている海パンは
祭具殿の秘宝!?
The swim trunks that Maebara-kun is wearing are a
highly-prized treasure from the festival storehouse?!
しかも取り返してくれたら―
And if you get them back for us, I'll give you a personal tour of the secrets hidden within the storehouse!
鷹野を祭具殿秘密見学ツアーに
ご招待なのです
んっ 乗ったわ
I'm in.
って どこから出したのよ
Where the hell did she get those?!
What flavor is today's curry?
（知恵(ちえ)）
今日のカレーはどんな味？
Not many people know that the shop at this pool is a three-star restaurant!
プールのカレーショップは
実は隠れた三ツ星店～
Hey, it's Chie-sensei!
あっ 知恵先生だ
Not even swimming, just fixated on curry... What a waste of a perfectly good body and swimsuit!
泳ぎもせずにカレーざんまいとは
豊満ボディーと水着が泣いてるね
Why, if it isn't Sonozaki-san and the others!  Hello there!  Are you all after some three-star curry as well?
あら 園崎さんたちですか
こんにちは
皆さんも三ツ星カレー狙い？
実は 知恵先生に
聞き逃せないお話がございますのよ
Actually, Chie-sensei, there's a little
something we simply must tell you...!
Oh?
えっ？
（沙都子）こしょ こしょ こしょ…
Is that true?!  Maebara-kun put
powdered curry in his swim trunks?!
それは本当ですか!?
前原君が海パンの中に
レトルトカレーを入れているって
He said it felt so cool and pleasant. Also, with
the curry smell, it works great as a deodorant!
ひんやりして気持ちよくて―
しかもカレーのにおいで
消臭効果もばっちりとか
H-He'll never get away with this!  It's blasphemy against curry!  God may forgive you, but I won't!!
ゆ… 許しません
カレーに対する冒涜(ぼうとく)です
神が許しても先生は許しません！
（魅音）だから そのＴ型定規は
どこから出したんだって
Seriously though, where the hell did she get those T squares?!
Sis!  How could you and the others come to the pool without telling me? If I find you, I'll give you such an earful...!
（詩音(しおん)）お姉たち 私に内緒で
プールに来るなんて許せない
見つけたら
とっちめてやるんだから
Shion!  Come help us out!
（魅音）詩音 あんたも手伝って
（詩音）んっ？
わああ！ って何よ いきなり
What the heck?!
Well actually...
実はね
（詩音）んっ？
ごにょ ごにょ
ごにょ ごにょ ごにょ…
Oh really...
なあるほど
ンフッ ンフフフッ 面白そう
Sounds interesting!
What!  Why the hell did you bring a stun gun to the pool?!
って あんた なんでプールに
スタンガン持ち込んでんの!?
At our school, they tell us to carry one at all times.
うちの学校では
常日頃から常備しておくようにって
Yeah right...
T-Today we are holding a social
gathering for the Angel Mort fanclub!
（オタク）
きょ… 今日はエンジェルモート
親衛隊の 親睦会なのでござる
It...It's not like we came to the pool
with perverted intentions or anything!
（オタク）
けけ… 決して いやらしい目的で
プールに来たんじゃないにゃりよ
刺激的な水着姿を見ても
耐えることを学ぶ精神修行にゃり～ん
We came here to learn how to steel our spirits and remain unfazed, even while looking at people in provocative swimwear!!
Ahh, just by watching these swimsuit girls, it feels like
I'm making a perfect V-form flight over the K-line!
（オタク）
はぅ～ もう水着ギャルたちを
眺めているだけで―
Ｖ字前傾飛行 Ｋ点越えっす～
（一同）んん～
Whoa, look over there!  It's Ryuuguu Rena and Sonozaki Mion!
うわっ あそこにいるのは
竜宮(りゅうぐう)レナ嬢と園崎魅音嬢！
さらに沙都子嬢と梨花嬢っす
Along with Satoko and Rika too!
There really are a lot of people in the Angel Mort fan club, aren't there?
まあ エンジェルモート親衛隊って
こんなに人数がいましたのね
ファーッファッファ
I'll have you know that there are no fewer than fifty participants at today's swimsuit viewing!
今日の水着鑑賞会には
実に50人もの参加があったっす～
That's perfect!
ちょうどいい
We'd love it if you would all help us out!
皆さんのお力を
ぜひお借りしたいんです
みぃ 圭一に―
Keiichi has burglarized our navy blue school swimsuits!
ボクたちの紺色スクール水着を
泥棒されてしまったのですよ
Whawhawhaaat?!!
（一同）にゃにゃにゃんと～！
He's been running around with the stolen swimsuits stuffed into his swim trunks!
圭一は 盗んだスク水を―
海パンの中に入れて
逃げ回っているのです
ゆゆゆ… 許せんでござーる
This is unforgivable!
To love them is legal, to steal them is shady -
to speak to us of moe is to reveal yourself as a fool!
めでるは合法 盗むは触法
萌えを語るは釈迦に説法！
梨花嬢と沙都子嬢のスク水を
股間に押し込むなど―
But to shove Rika-chan and Satoko-chan's school swimsuits into his pants... even if heaven forgives him, we shall not!
天が許しても
我々が許さんでござーる
We won't be satisfied by just catching him!
（オタク）捕まえるだけでは
飽き足りんて―
紺色スク水を取り返し
同じ悲しみを味わわせるため―
Once we get those swimsuits back, we'll make Comrade K experience the same pain by tearing off his swimsuit!
同志Ｋの海パンも
ひんむいてやるっす
総員突撃っす～！
（一同）うおお！
Everyone, charge!!
（オタク）突撃にゃり～！
I know we need to build up our forces, but these guys are just abominable.
いくら手勢を集めるためとはいえ
最低のやつらでございますわね
この際
ぜいたくは言ってられないよ
Beggars can't be choosers.
Looks like the magic of these swim trunks is the real thing!
どうやら この海パンの魔力は
本物みてえだな
If the trials are this bad, I can look
forward to reaping a huge reward afterward!
試練ってやつが これだけ強力なら
その御利益も期待できる んっ？
Hold it right there!  Let the nice lady give you a little shot!
お待ちなさ～い お姉さんが
優しくお注射してあげるわ
It looks like the grudge of all those unpopular men has taken control over Takano-san, too!
どうやら鷹野さんも―
モテない男たちの怨念に
取りつかれたようですね
Take that, and that, and that, and that!
そ～れ そ～れ そ～れ
そ～れ～！
んっ あら
なかなかやるわねえ 前原君
Well now...  Not too bad, are we, Maebara-kun?
（圭一）ふっ くあっ！
こ… 今度はＴ型定規かよ！
Now it's T squares?!
前原君 反省の時間が来ましたよ
Maebara-kun.  It's time for you to think about what you've done!
Now come, it's time to confess your
foolish sin of blasphemy against curry!
さあ カレーに対する冒涜
愚行を懺悔(ざんげ)なさい はあっ！
Stop!  Throwing!  T squares!!
だから… Ｔ型定規を…
投げるなっ だあっ
Oh dear, you're all sopping wet from playing in the pool.
あら プール遊びで全身びしょぬれ
（圭一）し… 詩音
Sh-Shion!
Which makes this thing here...
ってことは 一番効果的な武器は…
こいつってことになりますね
...the most effective weapon.  Right, Kei-chan?
圭ちゃん
Shion, you too?! But more importantly, a stun gun in a situation like this is no laughing matter!
し… 詩音まで あっ ていうか―
この状況でスタンガンは
シャレにならんだろうが
（知恵）んっ
（圭一）こ… ここは―
I think, in this situation... Escape is the winning move!
逃げるが勝ち～！
うわっ くっ お… お前らは!?
You guys!
We have misjudged you, Comrade K!
見損なったでござる 同志Ｋ
To steal a real schoolgirl's swimsuit is the w-w-worst!
リアル女学生の水着泥棒なんて
ささ… 最低にゃり～ん
You may say that, but your face gives your true feelings away!
とか言いながら未練タラタラ
その “うらやましいぞ
俺にも おすそ分けしろ”って顔―
Do something about that "I'm so jealous! Share it with me too!" face already!
何とかしろ！
If you can get Keiichi's swim trunks off, I'll give you my school swimsuit as a present!
圭一の海パンを脱がしてくれたら
ボクのスク水をプレゼントなのです
にぱ～
（一同）ひょええ！
Angel Mort's shining tomorrow...
the great and majestic Furude Rika.
エンジェルモートの輝ける明星
偉大なる古手(ふるで)梨花陛下…
（一同）万歳ー！
BANZAI!
（圭一）ああ… くう…
さすがにこの人数は こたえる
That's way too many people to deal with...  Is this the end?!
もはやここまで ジ･エンドか!?
Dammit, this sucks!!
チ… チクショウ 最悪だあ！
（入江(いりえ)）Ｋ 諦めてはいけない
（圭一）あっ
K!  You mustn't give up!
No matter how simple the thought or wish, it's all over the moment you give up!
（入江）
どんなに簡単な願いや思いも
諦めたら そこまで！
Are you going to give up on life's greatest
ambition because of a little trouble like this?
（富竹(とみたけ)）人生最大の野望を 君は
この程度のピンチで諦めるのかい？
God may forgive you for that, but the police never will!
（大石(おおいし)）そんなこと 神が許しても
警察は許しませんよ
あっ この声は！
These voices...!
Anyone who's born a man wants to someday be a ladies' man!
（富竹）男に生まれたからには
いつかはなりたいモテモテ男！
And you have the magical swim trunks
that can grant that wish!  Lovely, isn't it?
（大石）
それをかなえる魔法の海パン
すてきじゃないですか ンフフッ
What's more, once you wear it for three hours and the magic begins to act, the swim trunks will then pass to their next owner!
（入江）
しかも３時間はけば魔法が宿り
海パンは次の持ち主の手に渡る
ソウルブラザーズは
全員そろってモテモテを実現し―
We Soul Brothers will all become ladies' men and reach the ultimate world of moe and romance!
萌えとロマンの
究極世界へ至るのです
T-Tommy!  Cloud!  Irry, too!
と… トミー クラウド
そしてイリー！
The Four Divine Kings of Darkness have gathered!!
（入江たち）
暗黒四天王 ここに集結！
The Four Kings...but there's only three...
四天王って… ３人じゃん
No – Maebara Keiichi!
His name is nothing more than a mask.
いいや 前原圭一
彼の名も仮のものにすぎない
その真の名は…
His true name is...
The jet-black demon king...
漆黒の魔王！ んんっ… Ｋだ！
K!
And now we have four weirdos there.
また妙ちくりんな連中が
４人も そろっちゃいましてよ
Tommy!  Cloud!  Irry!  Thank you for rushing out to help me!
トミー クラウド イリー
ピンチに駆けつけてくれて
ありがとう
Don't mention it.
礼には及びません
We Soul Brothers – the Four Kings – will fend off anything you can throw at us!
我らソウルブラザーズ暗黒四天王
この程度の人数
防ぎきってみせちゃいますよ
Now...  If you're not scared of us, then bring it on!
さあ 僕たちが怖くなければ
かかってくるがいい
ヘヘヘッ こいつぁ心強いぜ
Now this is what I'm talkin' about...
この海パンは ソウルブラザーズ
みんなの財産にする
These swim trunks will become the fortune of all the soul brothers!
そして みんなで
モテモテを満喫するんだ！
And then we're all gonna max out our ladies' man potential together!!
You're terrible, Jirou-san!  You already have a woman like me, but you want to be popular with other girls, too?!
ひどいわ ジロウさん
（富竹）あっ
私という女がいながら
他の女の子にまでモテたいの!?
す… すまない 鷹野さん
I'm sorry, Takano-san.  But right now, I'm Tommy the Soul Brother!  Forgive me!
だが 今の僕は
ソウルブラザーズのトミーなんだ
許してくれ
Jirou-san...  If that's how you feel, then I won't hold back.
ジロウさん あなたがその気なら
もう遠慮はしない
（圭一）ひい！
んっ 出番よ 小此木(おこのぎ)！
You're up, Okonogi!
（小此木）
ヘヘヘッ 出番がなかったら
どうしようかと思ってましたわ
I was starting to wonder what I'd
do if I didn't appear in this episode!
O-Okonogi-kun!
お… 小此木君！
（圭一）はあ？
What the...?
T-They were wearing oxygen tanks and hiding in the bottom of pool the whole time?!
さ… 酸素ボンベ背負って―
ずーっとプールの底に
隠れてたわけですの!?
Okonogi-san, you switched over to Takano-san's side?!
小此木さんめ いつの間にか
鷹野さんに寝返っていたとは
ンッフフ～ となれば
こちらも容赦しませんよ
If that's how it's going to be, we'll show no mercy, either!
Go, riot squad!
そーれい！ 機動隊の皆さーん！
（オタクたち）うわあ！
（圭一）す… すごいぜ クラウド！
This is incredible, Cloud!
ンッフフ～
I've got professional soldiers over here!  What're the riot police to them?  Go wipe them out!!
こっちは戦闘のプロよ
機動隊が何よ せん滅しなさい！
ヒヒヒッ そりゃ難しいこってす
That would be difficult.  That's a fully armed riot squad; it'd be nice to at least get dressed properly before facing off with them.
向こうは完全武装の機動隊
せめて普通に服着て
対峙(たいじ)したいもんですわ
Geez...!  You're so useless!
もう この役立たず！
If that's the case, then leave it to me.
そういうことなら私に任せて
Kasai!
What the heck is that?!
な… 何だ ありゃ！
WATCH OUT, K!!!
危ない Ｋー！
くっ…
（圭一）ト… トミー！
T-Tommy!!
（富竹）あっ アハハハッ
僕の肉体は鉄壁なのさ
My body's made of steel!
You've got to be kidding me! That's a stun grenade! There's no way you should've been able to block that with your chest!
ありえなーい！
スタングレネード弾を
胸板で防ぐなんて ありえなーい！
どうしよう どうしよう
What're we gonna do now??
Kei-chan's being protected by the riot squad and our offense, Takano-san, was easily pushed back!
圭ちゃんの周りは
今や機動隊が守りを固め―
期待の戦力だった鷹野さんたちも
跳ね返されちゃったし
There's really nothing more we can do. Keiichi will soon become a wonderful narcissist-san!
実に もう
どうしようもないのですよ
もうすぐ圭一は―
すてきなナルシストさんに
なってしまうのです にぱ～
うっ ああ それはダメだよ
ダメダメダメ！
That's terrible! No, no, no!
We've run out of things to try...
もう万策尽きましたわ
うーん ソウルブラザーズの３人を
どうにかできれば…
If we could just do something about those three Soul Brothers...
あっ そっか！
Ah, I know!
Ooishi-san, there's something I want to talk to you about...
大石さん
お話ししたいことがあります
Oh, Ryuuguu-san, what might that be?
はて 竜宮さんが
私に何の話でしょうか？
Tomitake-ojisama?
富竹のおじさま～
（富竹）んっ 何だい？
Oh? What is it?
Director! Director! There's something I have to say...
監督 監督 実はお話が
えっ 何でしょうか？
沙都子ちゃん
Eh? What is it, Satoko-chan?
Why are they all being called away separately?
んっ なんで３人別々に
呼び出されてんだ？ んっ？
Um, you see... When we arrived at the pool, it was 9am.
（レナ）ええとですね
私たちがプールに来たの
実は９時からなんです
9am? Doesn't the pool usually open at 10am?
９時？ プールは朝10時からじゃ
ありませんでしたっけ？
ええっと 今日は特別な日で―
Um, today was a special day, so it opened an hour early.
いつもより
１時間早くオープンしたんです
Hmm? Which means that...
（大石）
おや？ ということはもう―
The ladies' man magic should have already taken effect.
モテモテの魔法が宿る時間は―
とっくに経過しているじゃ
ありませんか
Keiichi-san says that it's enough if he's the only ladies' man in the world.
圭一さんは
モテモテになるのは―
世界で自分１人だけで十分と
言っています
What?! Didn't we swear to all wear the ladies' man swim trunks and ride a surge of ladies' man-ness together?!
なんと！
モテモテの海パンを
みんなで はき合って―
共にモテモテの覇道を歩もうと
誓い合った―
その誓いは
ウソだったというのですか!?
Was that all a lie?!
しかも あの海パンには―
What's more, there's only one more dose of magic left in those swim trunks!
あと１回分しか
魔法が残ってないんですよ
な… 何だって!? ということは…
W-What?! This means...
After the next person wears it,
次に はいた人で…
（大石）モテモテの魔法は…
the ladies' man magic...
...runs out?!
終わり!?
Oh? What's wrong, you three?
んっ どうしたんだ？ ３人とも
You all have a weird look on your faces...
何だか
顔色が悪いように見えるけど
K, the Soul Brothers are a brotherhood of the soul.
Ｋ ソウルブラザーズは魂の兄弟
We share our dreams, our pain, our sadness together.
僕たちは すべての
夢も痛みも悲しみも共有する
（入江）そうです ですから
誰が勝っても負けても―
Precisely. So whoever loses or wins, we will all cry together, and rejoice together.
私たちと共に泣き 共に喜び合う
But to wish that that benefit would fall upon one's own is also not to be unexpected from a Soul Brother.
（大石）
しかし できればその御利益は
自分にありたいと思うのも また―
ソウルブラザーズとして当然のこと
Er, what did they tell you?
い… 一体 何 吹き込まれたんだ？
というか―
And... why are you all staring at my swim trunks?
なんで みんな
俺の海パン見てるんだ？
Y-You can't mean-!
ま… まさか！
Those swim trunks are mine!
（入江たち）
その海パンは いただきま～っす！
（圭一）痴漢ー！ ああ！
I'll take care of those swim trunks!
この海パンは私が預かります
モテモテの魔法は
もっとも私がふさわしい
That ladies' man magic is best off with me!
ここは肉体と肉体で
決着をつけようじゃないか
Let's settle this body to body!
All right! They got his swim trunks off!
やったあ！ 海パンを脱がせた！
Kei-chan!
圭ちゃん！
（梨花）ふにゅ～
Thank goodness! Thank goodness!
（魅音）
よかったあ よかったあ 圭ちゃん
間に合って本当によかった
I'm so glad we made it in time!
Thank goodness, my ass. I was
this close to being a ladies' man!
俺は全然よくねえぞ
あと少しでモテモテだったのに
全然違いますわよ
That's totally wrong! You were this close to becoming someone who would spend his life dangerously entranced by his mirror!
もう少しで圭一さんは
生涯 鏡を見つめて―
うっとり危険モードの―
かわいそうな人に
なっていましたのよ
Yeah! A Keiichi-kun with no interest in girls is no Keiichi-kun at all!
うん 女の子に興味が
なくなっちゃった圭一君なんて―
そんなの圭一君じゃないよ
じゃあ あの話って
本当だったのかよ!?
Wait, you were serious about that?!
That's right. There are people who would be sad if you lost interest in girls, you know.
本当なのです
圭一が 異性に
興味をなくしてしまったら―
悲しむ人もいるのですよ にぱ～
It really was dangerous there...
ほ… ほんとに
危ないところだったよ
I don't really get it, but I guess you guys saved me. Thanks.
何だか よく分からねえが
どうやら助けられたみたいだな
ありがとうよ
（魅音）うん
It all turned out right in the end, so I'll forgive you. And it turned out to be a really fun day too.
結果オーライだから
許してあげましてよ
それに断然楽しい一日に
なりましたもの
Yeah!
だよな アハハハッ
まだまだお昼だよ 圭一君
もっと いっぱい遊ぼ
It's still the afternoon! Let's keep on playing!
All right, let's go!
おーしっ やるか！
（魅音たち）あっ！
Um, Kei-chan? You're buck naked...
って あの 圭ちゃん
すっぽんぽんなんですけど
Hauu~! Keiichi-kun's fur seal! So cute!
はぅ～ 圭一君のオットセイ
かぁいいよお
げええ！
（梨花）大丈夫なのです
Don't worry! We've got the perfect swimsuit for Keiichi right here!
圭一にお似合いの水着が
ここにあったりするのですよ
それだけはイヤだー！
Anything but that...!!!
Give that to me...!
（羽入）
で 肝心の圭一の名前入り海パン
取り戻さなくていいのですか？
So, about those swim trunks with Keiichi's
name on them... shouldn't we take them back?
このままソウルブラザーズの誰かが
はいてしまったら…
If one of the Soul Brothers were to wear them...
（梨花）ンフフッ
Three hours from now, Keiichi will meet a wonderful "buddy"...
今から３時間後には
圭一とのすてきなバディの誕生ね
お… おぞましいのです
T-That's horrible! I don't want to
see a queer combination like that!!
そんなゲテモノ劇場
見たくもないのですよ
I'm the one best suited to be a ladies' man!
（入江）モテモテにふさわしいのは
この私だ！
（大石）見せつけてあげますよ
（富竹）もはや あなたには…
I'll show you how it's done!
（大石）ンフフッ
（入江）離せ
２人とも その手を離せ！
痛くないように、やさしく危めた
I gently ended , to stop the pain...
itakunai you ni, yasashiku ayameta
言葉に置き換えて、悲しみを忘れて
Changing it into mere words, I forget the sadness...
kotoba ni okikaete, kanashimi wo wasurete
あぁ、今、何を亡くしたのだろう？
But, ah, what have I now lost?
aa, ima, nani wo nakushita no darou?
罪という音の並びから　思い描かれた
Pictured by the sounds of my sins,
tsumi to iu oto no narabi kara  omoiegakareta
償うことも叶わない夢の記憶
this never-to-be-redeemed dream of a memory
tsugunau koto mo kanawanai yume no kioku
望まれたこの世界から　消えてなくなった・・・
vanished from this world that I had always longed for...
nozomareta kono sekai kara  kietenakunatta...
いつも既にかけている　人の祈り・・・
I have always been saying a human prayer...
itsumo sudeni kaketeiru  hito no inori...